[{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678819079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":12855,"timeElapsed":47067},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678826012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6931,"timeElapsed":54000},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678831666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5653,"timeElapsed":59654},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678837362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":5694,"timeElapsed":65350},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678840463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3100,"timeElapsed":68451},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678843470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3006,"timeElapsed":71458},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678847965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4493,"timeElapsed":75953},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678855238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7271,"timeElapsed":83225},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678863011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7772,"timeElapsed":90999},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678872485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":8194,"timeElapsed":100473},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678878453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5967,"timeElapsed":106441},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678881586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3131,"timeElapsed":109574},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678886563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4976,"timeElapsed":114551},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678890213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3649,"timeElapsed":118201},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678892769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2555,"timeElapsed":120757},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678897711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4941,"timeElapsed":125699},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678900666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2955,"timeElapsed":128654},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678903619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2952,"timeElapsed":131607},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678911634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7221,"timeElapsed":139622},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678913750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2114,"timeElapsed":141737},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678917523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3772,"timeElapsed":145511},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678921752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4228,"timeElapsed":149740},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678924337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2584,"timeElapsed":152325},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678926805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2466,"timeElapsed":154793},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678929539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2733,"timeElapsed":157527},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678937772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8232,"timeElapsed":165760},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678943198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5425,"timeElapsed":171186},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678951028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6920,"timeElapsed":179016},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678956741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5712,"timeElapsed":184729},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678959385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2644,"timeElapsed":187373},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678961661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2275,"timeElapsed":189649},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678965701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4039,"timeElapsed":193689},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678967409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1707,"timeElapsed":195397},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678969681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2271,"timeElapsed":197669},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678972200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2519,"timeElapsed":200188},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678974070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1869,"timeElapsed":202058},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678981139,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5654,"timeElapsed":209127},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678984023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2882,"timeElapsed":212011},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678987381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3357,"timeElapsed":215369},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678989449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2067,"timeElapsed":217437},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678996658,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7207,"timeElapsed":224646},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678999310,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2651,"timeElapsed":227298},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679001583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2272,"timeElapsed":229571},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679005021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3437,"timeElapsed":233009},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679008333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3311,"timeElapsed":236321},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679010633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2299,"timeElapsed":238621},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679016098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4582,"timeElapsed":244086},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679018375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2277,"timeElapsed":246363},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679020702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2325,"timeElapsed":248690},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679023236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2533,"timeElapsed":251224},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679027287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4050,"timeElapsed":255275},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679029534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2246,"timeElapsed":257522},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679034416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4881,"timeElapsed":262404},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679036285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1867,"timeElapsed":264273},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679038136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1850,"timeElapsed":266124},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679045784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6868,"timeElapsed":273772},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679047480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1696,"timeElapsed":275468},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679050677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3195,"timeElapsed":278665},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679052658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1980,"timeElapsed":280646},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679054541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1882,"timeElapsed":282529},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679056619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2077,"timeElapsed":284607},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679058905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2285,"timeElapsed":286893},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679060683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1777,"timeElapsed":288671},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679062314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1630,"timeElapsed":290302},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3612,"timeElapsed":294699},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679068308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1596,"timeElapsed":296296},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679071043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2734,"timeElapsed":299031},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679072342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1298,"timeElapsed":300330},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679076466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4122,"timeElapsed":304454},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679079458,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2991,"timeElapsed":307446},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679081943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2484,"timeElapsed":309931},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679084049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2105,"timeElapsed":312037},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1868,"timeElapsed":313906},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679087346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1427,"timeElapsed":315334},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679092797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4293,"timeElapsed":320785},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1368,"timeElapsed":322154},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679096865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2698,"timeElapsed":324853},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679097978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1113,"timeElapsed":325966},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679102688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4709,"timeElapsed":330676},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679105347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2658,"timeElapsed":333335},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679107939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2591,"timeElapsed":335927},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679109640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1701,"timeElapsed":337628},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679110564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":922,"timeElapsed":338552},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679117454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5903,"timeElapsed":345442},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679119613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2158,"timeElapsed":347601},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679121941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2327,"timeElapsed":349929},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679124712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2769,"timeElapsed":352700},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679126358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1646,"timeElapsed":354346},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679128576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2217,"timeElapsed":356564},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679130668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2092,"timeElapsed":358656},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679132118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1449,"timeElapsed":360106},{"subjectID":"kmdaa976dr","prolificID":"673ead8d8389b11c02a060e9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2f68d1b5a3852f93a4","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679134021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1902,"timeElapsed":362008}]